Friends, today we will talk
about the stock of III Bank. What support and resistance can be seen in the stock of III Bank
for the next trading week,
today in this video we will talk about it.
If we talk about the stock here, then
we will see that this stock has been
continuously
seen in a clear downtrend for a long time.
We are continuously
seeing a pattern of low and low, low and high in the stock here.
Even now we were seeing a recovery in the stock here,
but the stock could
not break its previous high here and we are again
seeing a gain of 0.31 in the stock here today. So,
if we talk about the stock from here, then
in the gain condition, we will
see the first support of the stock at here.
If the stock breaks it here, then
we will see the stock at 96. After this, we will see the
stock here and if the stock breaks it here, then from here
we will see the levels of the stock till
here.  We will go to the next
support brother, from here if there is a recovery in the stock then
in the recovery condition from here
we will get to
see resistance on the stock here, if the stock will rise
here then here
we will see the stock at 975, after this we will see the stock at 995,
after that we will again see the levels up to 110 in the stock
here as a
next resistance, so there are some
important levels in the stock, you can pay attention to them,
otherwise there
is no advice of buy, sell and holding in the video, the video is only for
educational purpose, thank you